var questions = [ // correctAnwer is undefined because it's in here and no longer reachable.
                // Maybe (key: value)  pairs in app.js aka  question[0]: correctAnswer: 1
    {
        question: "Why was TRON disqualified from receiving an Academy Award nomination for special effects?",
        answers:[
            "The producer was involved in a money laundering scandal.",
            "The Academy felt at the time that using computers was cheating.",
            "The film was released a few days too late to qualify.",
            "It didn't gross enough at the box office."
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Why did many Disney animators refuse to work on the film?",
        answers:[
            "They wanted to work on projects for the new Disney Channel.",
            "The Animator's Guild was planning a strike.",
            "They hated working with actors.",
            "They feared that computers would one day take their jobs."
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    // {
    //     question: "Flynn's game program is named CLU, which is an acronym for?",
    //     answers:[
    //         "Crispy Lightly-breaded Unicorns",
    //         "Computed Life-like Uni-code",
    //         "Codified Likeness Utility",
    //         "Computer Life Unity"
    //     ],
    //     correctAnswer: 2
    // },
    // {
    //     question: "Ram's light cycle in the book is green, but in the movie it rezzes up as what color?",
    //     answers:[
    //         "A lovely shade of Chartreuse.",
    //         "Blue",
    //         "Gold",
    //         "Red"
    //     ],
    //     correctAnswer: 3
    // },
    // {
    //     question: "Who was the film's director?",
    //     answers:[
    //         "Steven Speilberg",
    //         "George Lucas",
    //         "Steven Lisberger",
    //         "Ron Howard"
    //     ],
    //     correctAnswer: 2
    // },
    // {
    //     question: "Who wrote the novelization of TRON?",
    //     answers:[
    //         "Ernest Hemmingway",
    //         "Brian Daley",
    //         "Gregory Benford",
    //         "J. K. Rowling"
    //     ],
    //     correctAnswer: 1
    // },
    // {
    //     question: "What actor played the main character, Kevin Flynn/Clu, in the film?",
    //     answers:[
    //         "Beau Bridges",
    //         "Jeff Bridges",
    //         "London Bridges",
    //         "Harrison Ford"
    //     ],
    //     correctAnswer: 1
    // },
    // {
    //     question: "The star of TRON, Jeff Bridges, also played what other classic cult hit character?",
    //     answers:[
    //         "Flash Gordon",
    //         "Han Solo",
    //         "Mad Max",
    //         "The Dude"
    //     ],
    //     correctAnswer: 3
    // },
    // {
    //     question: "In What year did TRON hit theaters?",
    //     answers:[
    //         "1982",
    //         "1978",
    //         "1984",
    //         "1999"
    //     ],
    //     correctAnswer: 0
    // },
    // {
    //     question: "The sequel to the film was named...?",
    //     answers:[
    //         "TRON: Play Again",
    //         "TRON: Game Over",
    //         "TRON: Legacy",
    //         "TRONS"  
    //     ],
    //     correctAnswer: 2
    // }
];

module.exports = questions;




    